Speaker: Life in a day
Early in the morning in the USA, a baby opened his eyes and looked at his mother.
‘Isn’t he pretty?’ she asked the camera.
Around the world, people got up, and washed, and had breakfast.
A 15-yearold boy shaved for the first time. He didn’t enjoy it!
A boy kissed his mother on her birthday.
The 24th of July was a Saturday, so a lot of people didn’t go to work.
They relaxed and went to the park with their family, or went shopping.
But other people worked hard, or cooked and cleaned.
Some children played – but others worked. One small boy cleaned shoes in the street.
One woman went to hospital for an operation. Another woman waited all evening to talk to her husband on Skype.
He was a soldier thousands of miles from home.
For some people, the 24th of July was a special day.
A man arrived in Kathmandu. He was on a cycle trip around the world.
A woman did an incredible skydive.
An unemployed man got his first job.
A boy who was at university went home to see his father for the first time in three years.
Another man asked his girlfriend to marry him.
A man and a woman got married and had an incredible party.
This beautiful film shows us life around the world in the 21st century. Watch it! It’s free on YouTube